Rebecca West Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Correspondence, 1914-75; Series I; 11; (27 boxes)
  - REBECCA WEST CORRESPONDENCE
    - Hutton, Graham Hutton, Marjorie, 1960-68 (Box 10, Folder 421)
    - Huxley, Elspeth, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 422)
    - Huxley, Julian, 1933-47 (Box 10, Folder 423)
    - Huxley, Michael, 1938 Jul 26 (Box 10, Folder 424)
    - "I" general, 1951 Mar1 (Box 10, Folder 425)
    - International Association of Writers for the Defense of Culture, 1936 (Box 10, Folder 426)
    - International Writers' Conference, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 427)
    - Internationale Copyright Agentur, 1950 Mar 1 (Box 10, Folder 428)
    - Irvine, John, 1937 (Box 10, Folder 429)
    - Isbell, Eugenie, 1940 Aug 4 (Box 10, Folder 430)
    - "J" general, 1945-59 (Box 11, Folder 431)
    - J. Walter Thompson Co., 1950 (Box 11, Folder 432)
    - Jack, Alexia B., 1931-33 (Box 11, Folder 433)
    - Jacob, Ernest, 1932 Oct 24 (Box 11, Folder 434)
    - James B. Pinker and Sons, 1927-29 (Box 11, Folder 435)
    - James, William, Jr., 1943 Jun 4 (Box 11, Folder 436)
    - Jameson, Storm, 1934 (Box 11, Folder 437)
    - Jardine, Grace (with letter to Rona Robinson), 1942 (Box 11, Folder 438)
    - Jennings, Richard (The Daily Mirror ), 1942-43 (Box 11, Folder 439)
    - John Calder Ltd., 1958 (Box 11, Folder 440)
    - John Lane, The Bodley Head Limited, 1936 Jul 10 (Box 11, Folder 441)
    - Johnson, James Weldon, 1927 Oct 29 (Box 11, Folder 442)
    - Johnstone, David, 1929 Dec 10 (Box 11, Folder 443)
    - Johnstone, Patrick, 1937-39 (Box 11, Folder 444)
    - Jonathan Cape, 1939 (Box 11, Folder 445)
    - Jopson, R. Keith (?) Jopson, Francis, 1936-37 (Box 11, Folder 446)
    - Jordan, Mr., n.d. (Box 11, Folder 447)
    - "K" general, 1930-60 (Box 11, Folder 448)
    - Kallas, Arno, 1936 (Box 11, Folder 449)
    - Kapp, Yvonne, 1931 May 3 (Box 11, Folder 450)
    - Kang, Younghill, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 451)
    - Kauffman, Ruth, 1945-46 (Box 11, Folder 452)
    - Kaufman, Beatrice, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 453)
    - Kegl, Gisella, 1954 Apr 11 (Box 11, Folder 454)
    - Kennedy, Madge, 1927 Mar 18 (Box 11, Folder 455)
    - Kenney, Rowland (Box 11, Folder 456)
    - Kent, Madeleine, 1939, 1942 (Box 11, Folder 457)
    - Kind, A. N., 1958 (Box 11, Folder 458)
    - King, Marjorie A., 1956 May 12 (Box 11, Folder 459)
    - King's Lynn Museum, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 460)
    - Kingsley, Mary, 1939 Nov 24 (Box 11, Folder 461)
    - Kingsmill, Hugh, 1932-39 (Box 11, Folder 462)
    - Knobloch, Eddie, 1938-39 (Box 11, Folder 463)
    - Kremer, Michael, Dr. 1962, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 464)
    - Kuher, H., Monsignor, 1943-45 (Box 11, Folder 465)
    - Kuncewiczowa, Maria (with copy of article "Mon Romance avec la France," by Thadée Boy Zelenski), 1942 (Box 11, Folder 466)
    - "L" general, 1934-58 (Box 11, Folder 467)
    - Laffan, R., 1942 (Box 11, Folder 468)
    - Lambert, Amy B., 1932 (Box 11, Folder 469)
    - Lancaster, Osbert, Sir, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 470)
    - Landesregierung Schleswig-Holstein, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 471)
    - Landon, Walter, 1938-39 (Box 11, Folder 472)
    - Langner, Lawrence, 1933-36 (Box 11, Folder 473)
    - Lanham, Dorothy, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 474)
    - Larg, David Larg, Dorothy, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 475)
    - Laski, Harold Joseph, 1936 Jan 25 (Box 11, Folder 476)
    - Laski, Margharita, 1945 (Box 11, Folder 477)
    - Laver, James, 1938, 1940 (Box 11, Folder 478)
    - Lavery, John, 1928 Oct 24 (Box 11, Folder 479)
    - Lawrence, Frieda, 1930 (Box 11, Folder 480)
    - Lawson, Gladys (?), 1928 Jan 28 (Box 11, Folder 481)
    - Lawson, Nan, 1956 Mar 12 (Box 11, Folder 482)
    - LeBlanc, Georgette, 1931 (Box 11, Folder 483)
    - Leeds, Vera M. O., 1943 Jun 15 (Box 11, Folder 484)
    - Leeper, Janet, 1944 (Box 11, Folder 485)
    - Lehmann, Rosamond, 1953-55, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 486)
    - Leighton, Marie C., 1933 Sep 19 (Box 11, Folder 487)
    - Leighton, Stacy, 1931, 1938 (Box 11, Folder 488)
    - Leonard, Mary, 1940 Apr 26 (Box 11, Folder 489)
    - Leslie, Shane, 1931, 1955 (Box 11, Folder 490)
    - Lewis, Sinclair (with note by Dorothy Thompson), 1930 Aug 21 (Box 11, Folder 491)
    - Lewis, Wyndham, 1928-37 (Box 11, Folder 492)
    - Lincoln, Bishop of, 1937 Jul 23 (Box 11, Folder 493)
    - Linklater, Eric, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 494)
    - Linnehan, Edward G. (with related correspondence), 1954 (Box 11, Folder 495)
    - The Listener, 1946, 1955 (Box 11, Folder 496)
    - The Literary Guild of America, 1956 (Box 11, Folder 497)
    - Lloyds Bank, Limited, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 498)
    - Lofts, Norah, 1943-44 (Box 11, Folder 499)
    - The London Magazine, 1955 (Box 11, Folder 500)
    - Low, Barbara, 1937, 1945 (Box 11, Folder 501)
    - Low, David, 1933 (Box 11, Folder 502)
    - Lowinsky, Ruth Lowinsky, P. Lowinsky, Tommy, 1939-46, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 503)
    - Lowndes, Marie Belloc Lowndes, Susan, [1930]-40, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 504)
    - Lynch, Laurence P., 1959 (Box 11, Folder 505)
    - Lynd, Sylvia, 1946-51, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 506)
    - Lyons, Bertie, 1939 (Box 11, Folder 507)
    - "M" general, 1935-63 (Box 12, Folder 508-09)
    - Macaulay, Rose, 1957-58 (Box 12, Folder 510)
    - McBurney, Anne Charles McBurney, Charles, 1952-62 (Box 12, Folder 511-12)
    - MacCarthy, J. Dillon, 1961 (Box 12, Folder 513)
    - MacDonald, Duncan, 1937-42 (Box 12, Folder 514)
    - MacFie, Ronald Campbell, 1928 Jun 13 (Box 12, Folder 515)
    - MacGibbon & Kee, 1960 (Box 12, Folder 515a)
    - McGraw-Hill Book Company, Inc., 1955 Apr 5 (Box 12, Folder 516)
    - MacInnes, Helen (Highet), 1966 (Box 12, Folder 517)
    - MacKenzie, Compton, Sir, 1958 Jul 8 (Box 12, Folder 518)
    - MacKenzie, Margaret, 1967-68 (Box 12, Folder 519)
    - MacKenzie, Monty, 1968 Jun 19 (Box 12, Folder 520)
    - McLachlan, Donald McLachlan, Kitty, 1966-69 (Box 12, Folder 521)
    - McLaren, Moray, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 522)
    - McLean, Lian, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 523)
    - MacLeod, Alison, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 524)
    - MacLeod, Norman, 1936-53 (Box 12, Folder 525)
    - MacLeod, Norman, Jr. ("Bobby") (with related correspondence), 1947-53, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 526)
    - MacLeod, Winifred Fairfield, 1941-53, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 527-33)
    - McMaster, Ian McMaster, Jane, 1942-46 (Box 12, Folder 534)
    - MacMillan, Harold, 1957-68 (Box 12, Folder 535)
      See also: MacMillan and Company, Ltd. and Box 26, folder 1126
    - MacMillan and Company, Ltd, 1938-55 (Box 12, Folder 536)
    - MacNeish, James, 1958 (Box 12, Folder 537)
    - MacShane, Frank, 1962-63 (Box 12, Folder 538)
    - The Manchester Guardian, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 539)
    - Mander, Lady, 1969 May 12 (Box 12, Folder 540)
    - Mann, A. J., 1958 (Box 12, Folder 541)
    - Mann, Mary, 1957 Sep 20 (Box 12, Folder 542)
    - Manning, Ethel, 1931 (Box 12, Folder 543)
    - Manning, Olivia, 1967 Jan 5 (Box 12, Folder 544)
    - Marelic, Marcel M. A., 1945 Oct. 18 (Box 12, Folder 545)
    - Margerie, R. de, 1946 Feb 24 (Box 12, Folder 546)
    - Marks, Henry, 1938, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 547)
    - Martin, Kingsley
      See: The New Statesman and Nation, Box 13, folder 609
    - Martin, Nancy, 1959 Nov 20 (Box 12, Folder 548)
    - Martin, Ragun, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 549)
    - Martin Secker & Warburg Ltd., 1930-53 (Box 12, Folder 550)
    - Masaryk (?), Jan, 1939 May 17 (Box 12, Folder 551)
      See also: Box 26, folder 1168
    - Massingham, H. J., 1932 Sep 17 (Box 12, Folder 552)
    - Mathew, Theobald, 1945-61 (Box 12, Folder 553)
      See also: Charles Russell, Box 7, folder 201
    - Maud, John, Sir Maud, Jean, 1960-67 (Box 12, Folder 554)
    - Maugham, Syrie, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 555)
    - Maugham, W. Somerset, 1954 Oct 12 (Box 12, Folder 556)
    - Maxwell, W. R. M., 1960 (Box 12, Folder 557)
    - May, Mimi, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 558)
    - Medico-Legal Society, 1948-49 (Box 12, Folder 559)
    - Meloney, Marie M. ("Missy"), 1940 Jun 21 (Box 12, Folder 560)
      See also: New York Herald Tribune, Box 13, folder 611
    - Melville, Ruby, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 561)
    - Mervis, Ann Mervis, Gertrude Mervis, Joel, 1961 (Box 12, Folder 562)
    - Mervyn, William, 1967 Jun 12 (Box 12, Folder 563)
    - Metrick, Robert, 1961 Oct 20 (Box 12, Folder 564)
    - Milbank, M. V., Major, 1959 (Box 13, Folder 565)
    - Milford, Nancy, 1963-70 (Box 13, Folder 566)
    - Miller, Nellie, 1933 Apr 14 (Box 13, Folder 567)
    - Miller, Ruth, 1946 (Box 13, Folder 568)
    - Milroy, Dido, 1943 (Box 13, Folder 569)
    - Minister of Defence, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 570)
    - Ministry of Food, 1946-47 (Box 13, Folder 571)
    - Minney, R. James, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 572)
    - Mitchell, David, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 573)
    - Mitchell, Jonathan, 1965-69 (Box 13, Folder 574-75)
    - Mitford, Jessica, 1967 Feb 1 (Box 13, Folder 576)
    - Mitford, Nancy, 1961 (Box 13, Folder 577)
    - Mitgang, Herbert, 1965 Dec 28 (Box 13, Folder 578)
    - Mitrany, David, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 579)
    - Mizener, Arthur, 1965, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 580)
    - Monroe, Harriet, 1923 Dec 19 (Box 13, Folder 581)
    - Monteith, Charles
      See: Faber and Faber Limited, Box 8, folder 262
    - Moore, George, 1931-32 (Box 13, Folder 582)
    - Moore, Harry T., 1948, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 583)
    - Moore, Mary F., 1956 Mar 26 (Box 13, Folder 584)
    - Moorehead, Alan, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 585)
    - Morgan, Neil, 1962 May 24 (Box 13, Folder 586)
    - Morganstern, Dorothy, 1966 Jun 3 (Box 13, Folder 587)
    - Morris, John, 1935-67 (Box 13, Folder 588)
      See also: Encounter, Box 8, folder 256
    - Morris, Lloyd, 1928-38 (Box 13, Folder 589)
    - Mortimer, Raymond, 1948-58 (Box 13, Folder 590)
    - Moseley, Maboth, 1937 (Box 13, Folder 591)
    - Muggeridge, Malcolm, 1955 Aug 17 (Box 13, Folder 592)
    - Muller, Peggy, 1961-62, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 593)
    - Mumford, Lewis, 1968 Aug 19 (Box 13, Folder 594)
    - Munthe, Axel, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 595)
    - Murray, Gilbert, 1932 Oct. 19 (Box 13, Folder 596)
    - Murray, John C., 1958 (Box 13, Folder 597)
    - Murry, John Middleton, 1930 (Box 13, Folder 598)
    - "N" general, 1938-58, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 599)
    - Namier, Lewis Bernstein, Sir Namier, Julia, 1924-58 (Box 13, Folder 600)
    - Nash's Pall Mall Magazine, 1933-35 (Box 13, Folder 601)
    - National Book League, 1956 (Box 13, Folder 601a)
    - National Broadcasting Company, Inc., 1955-56 (Box 13, Folder 601b)
      With: untitled speech by Rebecca West, typescript, corrected, 1955 Sep 24
    - National Council for British-Soviet Unity, 1944 (Box 13, Folder 602)
    - Nekick, Jurs, 1955 May 15 (Box 13, Folder 602a)
    - Nesbitt, Cathleen, 1942, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 603)
    - Never Again Association, 1942-43 (Box 13, Folder 603a)
    - Neville, Edward, Rev., 1930 Oct 13 (Box 13, Folder 604)
    - The New English Library, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 605)
    - The New Leader, 1958 Jun 19 (Box 13, Folder 606)
    - New Masses, 1936 Jul 18 (Box 13, Folder 607)
    - The New Republic, 1936 Jul 17 (Box 13, Folder 608)
    - The New Statesman and Leader (with related information on Woodrow Wyatt controversy), 1946-47 (Box 13, Folder 609)
    - New York American, 1933-34 (Box 13, Folder 610)
    - New York Herald Tribune, 1928-32 (Box 13, Folder 611)
    - The New York Times (London), 1956 (Box 13, Folder 611a)
    - The New Yorker, 1928-53 (Box 13, Folder 612-17)
    - Newman, Ernest, 1928, 1931 (Box 13, Folder 618)
    - Nicholas, Elizabeth, 1958, 1961 (Box 13, Folder 619)
    - Nicholas Kaye, Limited, 1956 (Box 13, Folder 620)
    - Nicolai, Bishop, 1939 Jan 26 (Box 13, Folder 621)
    - [Nicols], Beverly, 1938 Feb 4 (Box 13, Folder 621a)
    - Nicolson, Harold George, Sir, 1932-56 (Box 13, Folder 622)
    - Nikolich, Miloye, 1946 Jul 27 (Box 13, Folder 623)
    - Nin, Anaïs, 1932-34, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 624)
    - Niven, Frederic, 1928 (Box 13, Folder 625)
    - Nott, S. C., 1956 Mar 13 (Box 13, Folder 625a)
    - "O" general, 1931-1955 (Box 14, Folder 626)
    - Ogilvy, David, 1932-47, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 627)
    - Ogilvy, Francis, 1927 May 31 (Box 14, Folder 627)
      With: deposition of David Oglivy and Philip Hendy, 1937
    - Ojencic, D. R., 1938 Jan 17 (Box 14, Folder 628)
    - Olaguer, Valdemar (with poems), 1949 Feb 19 (Box 14, Folder 629)
    - Oliver, Berta (Ruck), 1936, 1942 (Box 14, Folder 630)
    - Oliver, E. J., 1916 May 31 (Box 14, Folder 630a)
      With: "Henry James, O. M.," sonnet, printed version, 1916 Mar 31
    - Olivet College, 1939 (Box 14, Folder 631)
    - O'Neill, Carlotta Monterey, 1934 Mar 24 (Box 14, Folder 631a)
    - Onions, Berta
      See: Berta Oliver, Box 14, folder 630
    - The Outlook, 1930 (Box 14, Folder 632)
    - Oustram, Gioia, 1943 Dec 31 (Box 14, Folder 633)
    - Oxford University Press, 1933, 1946 (Box 14, Folder 634)
    - "P" general, 1930-57, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 635)
    - P. Corot and Company, 1948 Nov 23 (Box 14, Folder 636)
    - Pakenham, F., Lord (Box 14, Folder 637)
      See also: Box 27, folder 1180
    - Palmer, Nettie, 1930, 1935 (Box 14, Folder 638)
    - Palmer, Paul M., 1940 Aug 20 (Box 14, Folder 638)
    - Panich, S., 1946 (Box 14, Folder 639)
    - The Paris Review, 1956 Jul 14 (Box 14, Folder 640)
    - Parris, Henry, 1952 May 7 (Box 14, Folder 640a)
    - Parry, E., 1959 (Box 14, Folder 641)
    - Patch, Blanche (with copy of letter by Max Beerbohm), 1952 May 18 (Box 14, Folder 642)
    - Patmore, Derek
      See: Bollingen Foundation, Box 6, folder 151a
    - Payton, M. G., 1921 (Box 14, Folder 643)
    - Pearson, Norman Holmes, 1956 (Box 14, Folder 644)
    - Penguin Books, 1955-56 (Box 14, Folder 645)
    - Pertwee, Roland, 1956-58 (Box 14, Folder 646)
    - Pethick-Lawrence, E., 1933 Nov 15 (Box 14, Folder 647)
    - Petrol Controller, 1939 (Box 14, Folder 648)
    - Philips, Emanie
      See: Emanie Arling, Box 5, folder 60
    - Picture Post (Mr. Hutchinson), 1949 Mar 16 (Box 14, Folder 649)
    - Pinsent, Gerald H. S., 1938 Apr 30 (Box 14, Folder 650)
      See also: Box 27, folder 1182
    - Polish Pen Club (S. Zahorska), 1942 Dec 8 (Box 14, Folder 651)
    - Poljokan, Nina Salom, 1944 (Box 14, Folder 652)
    - Pontings, Limited, 1946 Jun 24 (Box 14, Folder 653)
    - Popular Television Association, 1953 Jul 18 (Box 14, Folder 654)
    - Potter, Nancy A., 1953 (Box 14, Folder 655)
    - Pound, Ezra, [1935] Dec 27 (Box 14, Folder 655a)
    - Pribichevich, Stoyan, 1945 (Box 14, Folder 656)
    - Price, J. T., 1960 (Box 14, Folder 657)
    - Priestley, J. B. (John Boynton), 1932-42 (Box 14, Folder 658)
    - Prichett, V. S. (Victor Sawdon), 1941-46 (Box 14, Folder 659)
    - Punch, 1955-58 (Box 14, Folder 660)
    - Quartermaine, Leon, 1928 May 17 (Box 14, Folder 661)
    - "R" general, 1924-59 (Box 14, Folder 662)
    - Radio Free Europe, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 663)
    - Ratcliffe, S. K., 1916-31, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 664-65)
    - Rawlings, Margaret (Lady Barlow), 1953-58 (Box 14, Folder 666)
    - Raymond, Anna, 1955 Oct 10 (Box 14, Folder 667)
    - Raymond, John, 1952 Mar 18 (Box 14, Folder 668)
    - Redisch, Walter Redisch, Mimi, 1939 (Box 14, Folder 669)
    - Rendel, George, Sir, 1945 (Box 14, Folder 670)
    - The Reprint Society, Ltd., 1958 (Box 14, Folder 671)
    - Rhondda, Margaret, Viscountess, 1927-40 (Box 14, Folder 672)
    - Rhys, Jean, 1931 Feb 17 (Box 14, Folder 673)
    - Richardson, Irene, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 674)
    - Riddell, Lord, 1928 Apr 6 (Box 14, Folder 675)
    - Rider and Company, 1956 (Box 14, Folder 676)
    - Riding, Laura, 1939 (Box 14, Folder 677)
    - Robert Hale Limited, 1955 (Box 14, Folder 678)
    - Roberts, C. E. B., 1946 (Box 14, Folder 679)
    - Robertson, Catherine C., 1959 Feb 10 (Box 14, Folder 680)
    - Robins, Denise, 1955 (Box 14, Folder 681)
    - Robinson, Anthony, 1946 (Box 14, Folder 682)
    - Robison, Robert K., 1946 (Box 14, Folder 683)
    - Roca, J. M. Batista, 1941 Sep 17 (Box 14, Folder 684)
    - Rodgers, John, 1942 (Box 14, Folder 685)
    - Romanovsky-Pavlovsky, Princess (Yugoslav Relief Society), 1941-46 (Box 14, Folder 686)
    - Roosevelt, Eleanor, 1951 (Box 14, Folder 687)
    - Rootham, Jasper, 1946 Jun 13 (Box 14, Folder 688)
    - Ross, Harold
      See: The New Yorker, Box 13, folder 612
    - Rotherham, G., 1944 (Box 14, Folder 689)
    - Rovere, Richard H., 1953 (Box 14, Folder 690)
    - Russell, Bertrand, 1967, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 691)
    - Russell, Leonard, 1959 Aug 19 (Box 14, Folder 692)
    - Ruthven-Murry, B., 1943 Aug 23 (Box 14, Folder 693)
    - Ruutuvoaen, Aulikki, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 694)
    - "S" general, 1927-69 (Box 15, Folder 695)
    - S. I. A., 1939 (Box 15, Folder 696)
    - Sachs, Emanie
    - Sachs, Hanns, 1932 (Box 15, Folder 697)
    - Sachs, Walter E., 1960 Dec 19 (Box 15, Folder 698)
    - Sackville-West, Edward, 1942-52 (Box 15, Folder 699)
    - Sackville-West, Vita, 1937-62 (Box 15, Folder 700)
    - Sadleir, Michael, 1940, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 701)
    - St. Clair, L. F. Stuart, 1961 (Box 15, Folder 702)
    - Salemar, Bertha, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 703)
    - Salomon, Virginia Salomon, William, 1962-67, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 704)
    - Salter, B., 1960 (Box 15, Folder 705)
    - Salzmann, Jerome, 1961 (Box 15, Folder 706)
    - The Saturday Evening Post, 1948 Jul 2 (Box 15, Folder 707)
    - The Saturday Review, 1948, 1955 (Box 15, Folder 708)
    - Saunders, Marion, 1944-58 (Box 15, Folder 709)
    - Savich, Slobodan, 1968-69 (Box 15, Folder 710)
    - Savic-Rebac, Anica, 1938-40 (Box 15, Folder 711-12)
    - Saxton, Mark, 1943 May 28 (Box 15, Folder 713)
    - Sayers, Dorothy, 1943 (Box 15, Folder 714)
    - Schefler, Magda, 1964-68 (Box 15, Folder 715)
    - Schell, Joseph, 1940 Sep 2 (Box 15, Folder 716)
    - Schlesinger, Arthur M., Jr., 1959-64 (Box 15, Folder 717)
    - Schrijver, Herman, 1969 Sep 3 (Box 15, Folder 718)
    - Schrirer, Essie, 1961, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 719)
    - Schorer, Mark, 1961 (Box 15, Folder 720)
    - Schustel, Lucy, 1939 Nov 22 (Box 15, Folder 721)
    - Schwartz, George, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 722)
    - Scott, Douglas, Mrs. ("Sappho"), n.d. (Box 15, Folder 723)
    - Seabrook, Phienka, 1942-66, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 724)
    - Searle, Alan, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 725)
    - Secker, Martin, 1966 May 31 (Box 15, Folder 726)
    - Selincourt, Irene, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 727)
    - Selous, Camilla, 1968-69 (Box 15, Folder 728)
    - Sencourt, Robert, 1969 Jan 19 (Box 15, Folder 729)
    - Senhouse, Roger, 1957 (Box 15, Folder 730)
    - Senlin, Ray, 1953 Mar 12 (Box 15, Folder 731)
    - Settle, Alison, 1968 Dec 12 (Box 15, Folder 732)
    - Sewell, Elizabeth, 1960-63 (Box 15, Folder 733)
    - Shackleton, Edith, 1946 (Box 15, Folder 734)
    - Shaw, Constance F., 1933, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 735)
    - Shaw, Bernard (with letters to H. G. Wells), 1916-21 (Box 15, Folder 736)
    - Shaw, Miss, 1933 Jun 19 (Box 15, Folder 737)
    - Shawcross, Hartley (with telegram to John Strachey), 1946, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 738)
    - Sheed and Ward Limited, 1951 (Box 15, Folder 739)
    - Sheldon, Dorothy, [1930] Nov 8 (Box 15, Folder 740)
    - Shepherd, Belle, Lady, 1962-64 (Box 15, Folder 741)
    - Sherek, Pamela, 1961 (Box 15, Folder 742)
    - Sherwood, Mary, 1961 Aug 2 (Box 15, Folder 743)
    - Shirer, William L., 1945 Oct 16 (Box 15, Folder 744)
    - Show, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 745)
    - Sibthorpe (Anglo-American Conference on Massacre of Jews), 1943 (Box 15, Folder 746)
    - Sieveking, Lance, 1946 (Box 15, Folder 747)
    - Simon, Andre L., 1944 (Box 15, Folder 748)
    - Simon and Schuster, Inc., 1956 Nov 16 (Box 15, Folder 749)
    - Simpson, John L., 1963 Jan 4 (Box 15, Folder 750)
    - Sinclair, Gillian, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 751)
    - Sinclair, Gregg M., 1962-65 (Box 15, Folder 752)
    - Sinclair, Upton, 1927 Jun 1 (Box 15, Folder 753)
    - Singh, Ansuyah, 1960-61 (Box 15, Folder 754)
    - Singh, Khushwent, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 755)
    - Sirefman, Josef P., 1965 (Box 15, Folder 756)
    - Sitwell, Georgia, 1967-69 (Box 15, Folder 757)
    - Slade, John, 1963, 1967 (Box 15, Folder 758)
    - Slade, Jope, Mrs., 1939 Jun 22 (Box 15, Folder 759)
    - Sladers, Dorothea, 1942 Mar 31 (Box 15, Folder 760)
    - Smith, Agnes (with photographs), 1944 Nov 26 (Box 15, Folder 761)
    - Smith, Charles W., 1948 Mar 5 (Box 15, Folder 762)
    - Smith, Timothy d'Arch, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 763)
    - Smith, Mr., 1965 Feb 1 (Box 15, Folder 764)
    - Snow, Carmel, 1931, 1954 (Box 15, Folder 765)
    - Snyder, Louis L., 1950 Nov 20 (Box 15, Folder 766)
    - Society for the Protection of Science and Learning, 1938-39 (Box 15, Folder 767)
    - Sokoloff, Alice Sokoloff, Boris, 1964, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 768)
    - Solomons, Bethel, Dr., 1960, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 769)
    - South Slav Democratic Union, 1965 Jul 19 (Box 15, Folder 770)
    - Spalek, John N., 1964 Feb 10 (Box 15, Folder 771)
    - The Spectator, 1938, 1948 (Box 15, Folder 772)
    - Spicer and Pegler, 1950 Aug 22 (Box 15, Folder 773)
    - Spink & Son, Ltd., 1969-70 (Box 15, Folder 774)
    - Spark, Muriel, 1967-68 (Box 15, Folder 775)
    - Spargo, Mary, 1964-65 (Box 15, Folder 776)
    - Staterman, Richard, Mrs., 1962 (Box 16, Folder 777)
    - Stead, Christina, 1937 Mar 11 (Box 16, Folder 778)
    - Steele, Max, 1947 Jun 18 (Box 16, Folder 779)
    - Steinbrecher, George, Jr., 1967 (Box 16, Folder 780)
    - Stephenson, Harwood and Tatham, 1950 Oct 11 (Box 16, Folder 781)
    - Stern, Fritz, 1968 Dec 15 (Box 16, Folder 782)
    - Stern, G. B., 1927-40, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 783)
    - Stevens, Doris, 1938-62 (Box 16, Folder 784-93)
      See also: Jonathan Mitchell, Box 13, folder 574
    - Stevenson, F. L. (Lady Lloyd George), 1937 (Box 16, Folder 794)
    - Stirling, Gertrude, 1937 Oct 20 (Box 16, Folder 795)
    - Stirling, Monica, 1946 (Box 16, Folder 796)
    - Stock Femina Vie Heureuse & Heineman Prize Committee, 1939 Dec 4 (Box 16, Folder 797)
    - Stokes, Sewell, 1927-28 (Box 16, Folder 798)
    - Storey, Angela, 1957 (Box 16, Folder 799)
    - Story and the Story Press (Whit Burnett), 1948 Jan 7 (Box 16, Folder 800)
    - Strachey, Anne, 1930-39 (Box 16, Folder 801)
    - Stratton, Arthur, 1964-65 (Box 16, Folder 802)
    - Straus, Ralph, 1942-43 (Box 16, Folder 803)
    - Sullivan, Frank, 1939 Dec 10 (Box 16, Folder 804)
    - Sutherland, Graham, 1966 Aug 8 (Box 16, Folder 805)
    - Sutton, William A., 1969-70 (Box 16, Folder 806)
    - Sweet, Blanche (Hackett), 1946 (Box 16, Folder 807)
    - Swing, Betty G., 1960-62 (Box 16, Folder 808)
    - Sword of the Spirit, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 809)
    - "T" general, 1938-54 (Box 16, Folder 810)
    - Tanner, P. A., 1965 (Box 16, Folder 811)
    - The Tate Gallery, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 812)
    - Taylor, A. J. P. Taylor, Eve, 1955-68, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 813)
    - Taylor, W. W. J., Rev., 1958 (Box 16, Folder 814)
    - Tennent, Paola, 1963-68 (Box 16, Folder 815)
    - Theis, Louise, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 816)
    - Thomas, Lida (with related correspondence), 1940-64, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 817-20)
    - Thomas, Maureen, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 821)
    - Thompson, Allan R., 1965-69 (Box 16, Folder 822)
    - Thompson, Dorothy (with related letters from Dinah Sheean), 1937-59 (Box 16, Folder 823-25)
    - Thorndyke, Sybil, Dame (Box 16, Folder 826)
    - Thornton, Philip (with related correspondence), 1937 (Box 16, Folder 827)
    - Tickell, Margaret A., n.d. (Box 17, Folder 828)
    - Time and Tide
      See: Margaret, Vicountess Rhondda, Box 14, folder 672
    - Time-Life International, 1947 (Box 17, Folder 829)
    - Tinckler, Charles C., 1941, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 830)
    - Toledano, Ralph de Toledano, Nora de, 1965-67 (Box 17, Folder 831)
    - The Tolstoy Society, 1933 (Box 17, Folder 832)
    - Tomlinson, H. M., 1937 Feb 23 (Box 17, Folder 833)
    - Topolski, Feliks, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 834)